. . . . . .
Thank you.
Okay, alright
Mode nash no survival
day Get away from Go,
go, go I don't wanna fail
Let's go, go 1, 2, 3 Come
and find a way Life for me
this is looks like
you're finally awake was
everything we've seen
before a dream yeah to
distract us from being
dissolved in this room
break the door quickly use
your power star platinum
It's open!
Pull me out of here!
We have to leave this room right away!
Hold on.
What was that you said just now?
Did you say Star Platinum?
That's my stand.
Jolene, how would you know that?
From what I can tell, it only became
reality after I told you about John Gloria.
In other words, there's no way
you could have seen my power yet.
Even if you feel it's existence
since you're my child,
there's no way you should
know the name Star Platinum.
That would be inconsistent.
This isn't reality.
Stone Ocean.
man.
Jolene.
About time.
You finally snapped out of it.
I had to push myself.
My thread
dissolves so fast.
Jolene, were you dreaming too?
No, I've been in a nightmare. Then I woke
up to all of this.
Yes, I see.
Looks like we were both
being shown specific visions.
Like
watching a movie. Sounds right.
If only we had some
popcorn, it'd be perfect.
I can't Move anymore?
Not a finger.
What about you?
Can you move?
The current situation could be a dream.
Within another dream.
If you can't move at
all, then it's reality.
A harsh reality.
One which we might not escape.
Yes. I see.
At this rate, we're screwed.
Dead meat.
The power of the
Pendant.
Bring out the stand that
you just used to wake me up.
Stone Ocean?
That's right.
Can you bring it out in a clump?
Basically, your strength...
It's no good.
I know that.
It took everything I had just to wake you.
There's no help of opening the door.
That's fine.
Just bring it out.
Yes. Like that. Keep going.
Can you bring it out further?
Just a bit more.
Bring it a little closer to me.
It would be for the best if you could
shift it over a little further to my left.
That should work.
It's not what I'd call
ideal, but it's close.
This should at least
help us get out of here.
That was Star Platinum.
It's my stand.
Now then, pull me out.
This is reality.
Make no mistake.
You bastard!
Damn you!
That hurt!
This pain I feel and this irritation!
Bastard, how dare you!
This irritation I'm feeling!
There's no way this
could be a hallucination!
Good. Lift your hands.
What is it now?
Let's go.
Oh, right.
Do you know what this is?
Whatever it is, we were
saved because of it.
That's a human bone.
Further, it's a part of the pelvis
called the sacrum from an adult female.
Based on the surface condition,
it seems to have been
dissolved by some kind of acid.
It's been dissolved?
You mean the same stuff? Who knows?
I have no clue why you'd carry
something like that around,
but it doesn't matter right now.
I was the only one who saw
him, but the kid exists.
It's a mystery, but this is
proof that he's actually here.
Code 909, security level 4.
Abnormality detected
outside the visiting room.
Security level 4.
Code 909.
What are we gonna do?
Because once we left that room,
you became a wanted criminal.
Like I said from the start,
I'm getting you out of here.
You have it, right? The pendant?
That thing's more important
than it looks, so don't lose it.
Now then, breakout time.
I never would have guessed
it escaped my trap!
Not many guards. What's that about?
This is a semi-public area.
Take a look.
Our goal is a window at the western wall.
The window faces out to the shore,
and from there we'll escape to
the outside world via submarine.
A submarine?
I have a little connection with the
organization called the Speedwagon Foundation.
They've arranged it for us.
I'm not seeing any
cameras in this hallway.
The window is just down this
junction here, to the left.
From the window to the shore
is just under 20 meters.
I'm sure you have a lot
on your mind right now,
but we have to focus on getting outside.
Let's go.
It was that van.
Chulene.
It hurts!
Where are you looking? Don't rush.
Here, stand up.
Go ahead.
Take my hand.
I'm okay. Just clumsy.
But thank you.
I can stand up on my own without any help.
That isn't it.
It's this.
Be more careful when you trip next time.
What are you going to do if
this flies away or you lose it?
What's wrong I told you this was
important so hold on to it here
You're really going to Tokyo
despite everything our daughter is
having to go through right now What
kind of father are you Hello Hello
You haven't changed, have you?
You're always thinking everything
through calmly and logically.
Even when I was a kid
dying of a high fever,
you couldn't be bothered to come see me.
Or when I was doing a little joyriding
and they accused me of stealing the car.
You were on an airplane heading
somewhere exotic instead.
Yet somehow, I still
grew up safe and healthy.
I mean, even now,
I'm a troublemaker that doesn't get
hurt no matter how many times I fall!
So lucky! Woo-hoo!
What are you going on about?
If it's important, hold onto it yourself!
Jolene…
Shut up!
It's a bit late for…
Not that.
Have you not noticed yet?
Something has been following us, quietly.
Jolene, get down.
Nobody down this hallway.
I guess they must have gone the other way.
It's a guard. What's he?
Hey, what's that?
Something forced its way
past this metal gate.
The prisoner has to have
gone this way. Come in!
Wait, is that...
Jean Gloria!
It's him!
He came to take care of us himself!
Jolene!
Keep heading to the window!
I'll face off against him!
That's John Gallier's stand.
But I thought his attacks
had only been a dream. Die!
Is this still a dream?
It's not! This is happening! Time stopped!
The enemy.
I think there were two of them.
It conjured visions for Jolene and I.
It even went so far as to put John Gallier's
actual stand Inside of those dreams.
Everything had been a
set up To lead to this!
Set up precisely for this moment Where I'd
have no other options But to stop time!
To keep my daughter safe.
Their target
Was always me.
Time is about to start? Jolene!
Looks like you were one
step too late, Jotaro Kujo.
I've waited for this.
Wish I could take my time.
It seems they were already done.
Perfect.
Even the invincible Joestar couldn't stop
me from obtaining that which I wanted.
You were no match for
the power of Palesnake!
The shooter's still up!
It's a stand!
What the?
But I thought his stand was just a dream!
Anyway, let's move while
he's still reloading!
There's the shore!
We're almost out!
You go ahead.
I'll catch up.
Huh? Let's go! Hurry!
Come on!
Listen.
There can only be one stand per person.
So then, there were two
enemies from the beginning.
John Gallier's one.
The Mushy Guy, the second.
Take this pendant and get out
of here while you still can.
Don't drop it.
A transmitter has been
fitted inside of the pendant.
So they can determine your location?
The submarine has been programmed to find
and follow this signal automatically.
It homes in like a beacon!
Do you understand what I'm saying, Jolene?
Just go to the shore and the submarine
will come to you, easy as that.
From there,
the speed wagon foundation that I mentioned
Will come and take you somewhere safe?
You got that?
Now, go.
You mean this thing?
Earlier, I...
I didn't know.
But you...
I want you to know.
You were always incredibly
important to me.
You.
Hey, what the hell? Your chest.
It can't be.
But how?
You can't. Go.
Jolene, I'm only bleeding a little.
I'll catch up to you in no time.
Don't lie!
All because you protected me earlier.
The other enemy took
something away from you.
And that's why you
couldn't dodge the bullets.
Is that it?
What did he take?
Could it be your stance?
Chulene!
No way!
Hey, what is this?
This thread is...
When did it...
I've got you!
Be quiet.
We're getting out of here.
We're heading to the shore
to make our great escape.
So don't interfere. Got it?
Wait, the girl.
When did she acquire this kind of stand?
A stand as powerful as this one.
Should have already been investigated
before she entered the facility all right.
I'll drop the gun
Simon didn't say drop it.
I was just checking out
the angles I wanted to make
sure to line up the easiest
one to hit you from See,
I'd prefer if your jaw were facing
a little further to the right.
If I knew she was this powerful,
I would have taken care of her
first before going after Jotaro!
It was my mistake to
make him my first target!
Is Pale Snake already aware
of this turn of events?
Jolene Kujo!
There's no doubt that
she's Jotaro's daughter!
A part of the Joestar Line!
Jolene. Earlier.
When we were still stuck in that dream,
you said you would stay
here in this prison for
the sake of a child that
you don't even know.
He grabbed me as if he
depended on me. That's why.
I'm going back in. I know now.
What I saw was just a dream.
And yet...
Dad! Damn it!
We nearly made it to the shore! Hey, Dad!
Get up!
Find them!
Gently force authorized!
A guard has been shot!
The criminal is armed and dangerous!
If it comes to a shoot to kill!
Where is it?
We're at the shore!
Come on.
That Speedwagon Foundation.
You say you've got some kind
of connection with them?
I have no idea who they are.
But if a submarine is
really going to come for us,
then they must have considerable financial
assets and technological capabilities.
This wound, hit by a ricochet
bullet, they'd have to help.
Surely they'd be able to treat it
better than any regular doctor.
Where is the submarine?
Where are you?
So everything you told me was true.
The submarine was already
here and waiting for us.
We're in the clear!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
No way.
It...
it can't be.
No, there's no way.
Even if he got shot, the wound is shallow.
None of his vitals were hit.
It's not supposed to be a fatal wound.
But... but...
Why are you...
Why the hell did your
heart stop beating dead?
See? I can tell.
You've got the blood of a Joestar. Go.
You've got a good head on your shoulders.
You can make it on your own, right?
We got him!
I see some movement on the
other side of the fence!
Watch out for the gun!
Hey, I'm not on the
other side of the fence.
I'm right here.
If you're talking about me, that is.
You bitch!
Hold on, don't shoot.
She has her hands up. Yeah, but...
Do not fire! She's unarmed.
Do you surrender?
But there should be another person.
The tall man with a cap
who came to visit her.
He's close.
Go find him!
I see.
That's where you were?
Why
didn't you run?
It's a tragedy!
But your father is
already as good as dead.
His powers were taken
by that weird mushy guy.
He barely survived the trap
he set for your father.
So why?
Why didn't you escape?
Because the The one who
did it went back inside.
Not outside, but inside.
The culprit's goal relies
on their ability to
steal people's stands by
making them materialize.
That mushy bastard deliberately
went back inside of the prison.
They didn't try to make a run for it,
so they must have what they
need inside the prison.
And so what?
You can't possibly think
you can get it back.
Do you really think your dad
will come back to life if you do?
That's why I'm going back in.
I don't want to be the one to tell
you, but a dead body just rots.
That bone I gave you was from my mom.
He took her soul as well.
She died.
I see.
My mother gave birth to me
while she was a prisoner here.
And I've been hiding in
this prison ever since.
Your name, tell me.
Oh, I'm Emporio.
Emporio.
Well, I was able to survive
because of your mother.
Thank you.
You know, I have this
unexplainable confidence.
I don't believe my
father is actually dead.
I think he'll be okay if
I can get his stand back.
That's why.
I'm staying.
We did it.
Now we have the mighty stand
with the ability to stop time.
Yes, and we couldn't have done
it without you, Johngalli.
You and I make quite a formidable duo.
Agreed.
Now, could you help me
back to the men's prison?
I hadn't anticipated.
That's strange.
Where's my gun?
Can you see it?
It's right here.
You were the only one that
knew my true identity.
And it just so happens you were
the one who murdered that guard.
With this everything
will work out very nice.
To be able to communicate
an idea to someone,
Jotar himself had said what
a wonderful thing it was.
And he was right.
I have the proof right here.
Thank you.